Jayden Owens

Software Developer

Eagle Mountain, UT 84005 jaydenowens23@gmail.com +1 435 201 3315

As a developer with 3 years of experience in multiple frameworks such as react, angular, and asp.net. And over 3 years experience using coding languages such as JavaScript, typescript, php, C#, Ruby, and some experience with swift and kotlin. I have the knowledge and skills to help your company grow.

Authorized to work in the US for any employer

Work Experience

Software Developer

EscrowTech International-Lehi, UT December 2022 to Present

Working with Angular, php, sql, and more. As a developer i maintain and build upgrades on company websites and help create a great customer experience.

Lead Software Developer(part time/evenings)

Scrybe Streaming.-Phoenix, AZ February 2021 to Present

Working with Scrybe i have been the lead decision-maker for all software-related issues since Febuary 2022. i was incharge of created developer team and transitioning from the current off shores team to a new interally built team. since starting ihave helped with the rebuild of our mobile app, built 2 new web applications, and made several updates to AWS.

Software Developer

Impartner Software-South Jordan, UT August 2021 to November 2022

Using asp.net and angular I help the implementation team respond to customer bugs and enhancements of features. While also helping with new features for all customers. As a scrum master, I lead meetings daily to help my team with blockers and maintain a steady workflow.

Mobile development instructor

Eduonix-Remote

June 2021 to September 2021

Freelance job teaching a course on mobile development for kids. An entry level course using mit app inventor.

Senior Officer

Tooele County Jail-Tooele, UT August 2020 to August 2021

Tooele, Utah USA 08/2020

- > Working in a team of 5-7 officers I have learned to balance priorities with time sensitive objectives and higher priorities.
- > Having been in law enforcement for 5 years I act as a senior officer.
- > As a senior officer I make decisions and are given tasks that are more difficult then others.
- > Entering new arrest data into applications to keep track of offenses and other information.
- > Writing reports on incidents throughout the night.

Correctional Officer

Sevier county jail-Richfield, UT June 2018 to August 2020

Working in a team of 2-4 officers I would help run a small facility.

- > Using verbal communication to help resolve problems with inmates and officers.
- > Using communication skills to de-escalate high stress situations between combative people and my self
- > Entering new arrest data into spillman, cjis, and other applications.

Education

Certificate in Web Development

Dev Point Labs - Salt Lake City, UT February 2021 to May 2021

High school diploma or GED

Skills

- Web Development Java Script
- Html
- Json
- React
- Postgresql
- Css
- Styled Components Ruby on Rails
- C#
- Xamarin
- APIs
- MySQL
- Git
- · Agile
- XML
- GitHub
- Bootstrap

- Software deployment
- .NET Framework
- Node.js

Additional Information

Portfolio

https://jaydenowensportfolio.netlify.app